迈克:因为得了流行性感冒,有几位老师今天将缺堂,他们的课程要被取消.哦,我太紧张了,凯特,你读他们的名字吧.
Mike: Due to the continuing flu epidemic, the following teachers will be out today, and
their classes cancelled.Oh, Kate you read 'em, I'm too nervous
凯特: 福若斯特教授,化学和生物实验室.
Kate: Professor Forrest, Chem.and Bio labs.
迈克:哦,我知道我本应该上化学课的.
Mike: Oh, I knew I should have taken Chemistry.
凯特:乔斯小姐的英语课.
Kate: Miss Gorse's English seminar.
迈克:我们喜欢的索恩教授会来吗?
Mike: Is our beloved Professor Thorn up there?
凯特:会.
Kate: Yes.
迈克:哦!太好了!
Mike: Oh yes!Alright!No Drama!
没有戏剧课.我们希望不仅仅只是24个小时.
Let's hope it's not just one of those twenty four hour deals.
凯特:迈克,我们现在正在谈论的是一个人,人类.
Kate: Mike, this is a person we're talking about, a human being.
迈克:他不是人类,他是老师.
Mike: He's not a human being, he's a teacher.
凯特:哦,迈克,有个好建议可以让你不要那么闲.因为流行性感冒,高中的替补老师在这个星期必须穿过长岛.
Kate: Oh, Mike, here's a good idea to keep you busy; due to the flu
epidemics, substitute high school teachers needed this week throughout
Long Island
迈克:继续说.
Mike: Go on.
凯特:我正要说,你可以去做替补老师.
Kate: Well that's it, you could substitute teach.
迈克:你不要在那信口雌黄了.
Mike: You should be in bed young lady.
凯特:迈克,我是认真的.
Kate: Mike, I'm serious.
迈克:那好,给我一个好的理由告诉我为什么我要去教书?
Mike: Well, give me one good reason why I should...teach.
凯特:因为它的酬劳是50美元一天.
Kate: Pay is fifty Dollars a day.
迈克:哦,那是一个理由.
Mike: Ooh, that's one.
凯特:替补老师将会辅助准备包括数学,历史,
Kate: Substitutes will administer prepared lessons in subjects including
戏剧的课程.
Mathematics, History, Drama!
迈克:戏剧课!太好了,我可以…哦,但是凯特,我!教书!我是一个不喜欢教书的人.
Mike: Drama!Well, I could err...Oh, but Kate, me!Teach!I'm the Anti-Teacher.
凯特:嗯,
Kate: Well, it wouldn't be a bad idea down the road to have another skill
但是在人生的道路上你可以多掌握一门技能也不是一个坏主意.
to fall back on.
迈克:凯特,我想成为一个演员,我不需要什么技能.
Mike: Kate, I wanna be an actor, I don't need a skill.
玛吉:哦,宝贝!你感觉哪里不舒服吗?
Maggie: Oh, hi honey, how are you feeling?
开萝尔:我看起来怎么了?
Carol: How do I look?
本:我去帮你叫医生.
Ben: I'll call the paramedics.
玛吉:你能吃点东西吗?
Maggie: Think you can finally keep some food down?
开萝尔:那你做了什么东西吃?
Carol: Well what are you making?
玛吉:豌豆汤.哦,妈妈,你好吗?玛吉, 开萝尔生病了,我们其他人都还好.我正要告诉你,我们将送另外一张克丽丝的录像带给你.不要,妈妈.它比最后那张短很多.我想你会喜欢的.哦,你好,爸爸.
Maggie: Pea soup.Oh, hi Mom, how are you doing?Maggie.Well, Carol's got that
bug that's going around, but the rest of us are fine.I just wanted to
tell you, we're about to send another video tape of Chrissy.No, Mom, it will
be shorter than the last one.I thought you liked it!Oh, hi Daddy
克丽丝:妈妈.
Chrissy: Mamma.
玛吉:你不要等那张录像带了.爸爸,快听,克丽丝说话了.
Maggie: You won't have to wait for the video tape, Dad, Chrissy's talking now, just listen.
克丽丝:妈妈.
Chrissy: Mamma.
玛吉:克丽丝,向爷爷奶奶问好.
Maggie: Chrissy, say hello to you Grandparents.
克丽丝: ****!
Chrissy: ****!
玛吉:哦,爸爸,杰森还没教她向您打招呼.
Maggie: No, Daddy, Jason didn't train her to say that to you.
您说得很对,我应该去找个人回来教她说话.一定,
Well you're darn tooting I'm gonna find out who taught her to say that.
爸爸.再见.本杰明西维尔.
Sure Dad.Bye.Benjamin Seaver.
本:妈妈,放松一下.我把它都录下来了.
Ben: Relax Mom, I got it all on tape.
玛吉:你曾经在克丽丝面前说过那个字?
Maggie: Have you been using that word around Chrissy.
本:哦,嗯…嗯…
Ben: Oh, err...well...
杰森:大家好.
Jason: Hey everybody.
本:爸爸,我的天啊,你还好吗?
Ben: Dad, Well gosh darn it, heck, anyway how are you?
杰森:本,你做什么了?
Jason: Ben, what did you do?
本:不是我,是她.
Ben: It's not me, it's her.
玛吉:克丽丝学了一个词.
Maggie: Chrissy learned a new word.
杰森:哦!一个新的词!天啊,克丽丝!
Jason: Oh!A new word!Oh, Chrissy!
玛吉:对,但是...
Maggie: Yes, but err...
杰森:把相机给我.说爸爸!对了,这里,克丽丝,我是谁啊?
Jason: Give me the camera.Say Dadda!Yes over here.Chrissy, who am I?
克丽丝: ****!
Chrissy: ****!
杰森:她刚刚说…
Jason: Did she just say...
玛吉:是,她说了.本,是不是啊?
Maggie: Yes, she did.Didn't she, Ben?
本:爸爸,因为我做了一些事情所以妈妈就有这种疯狂的想法.
Ben: Dad, Mom has this crazy idea that somehow I had something to do with this.
杰森:哦,天!
Jason: Uh hu!
本:哦,我是清白的!我发誓!不是我.
Ben: Hey, I'm innocent!I swear!No I don't.
杰森:哦,假如谁教坏她,那么那个该死的家伙是谁?哦,克丽丝.玛吉,迈克!
Jason: Well, if somebody's taught her bad and who ever the hel...Oh, Chrissy.Maggie.Mike!
天哪!你怎么了?
Gosh, darn it, the heck, how are you?
迈克:爸爸, 今天是我这一年,整个学期最坏的一天.
Mike: Dad, this was the best day of the whole semester, my entire year!
杰森:哦,是吗?怎么了?
Jason: Oh, really?Why?
迈克:今天没课.所有的老师都病倒了.哇,开萝尔,今晚很热吗?
Mike: Well, no classes.All my teachers were sick.Wow, Carol, hot date tonight?
开萝尔:哦,迈克,我留了一个电话留言给你.
Carol: Oh, Mike, I took a phone message for you.
迈克:是吗?太好了,在哪呢?
Mike: Oh, good, where is it?
开萝尔:我把它给撕掉了.
Carol: I tore it up.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
开萝尔:因为我以前总是留字条给你,
Carol: Because I always do that.But this one I'll tell you about.
但是这次我要告诉你它的内容.
You're expected to report to Principal Dewitt's office at Dewey high tomorrow
明天早上 他们希望你去杜威尔高中的校长办公室高中报道.
morning.
杰森:什么?等一下,为什么他们要让你回以前的高中?
Jason: What!Wait, why would they want you back at your old high school?
开萝尔: 我想唯一的理由就是他们重新查了你的学校.
Carol: The only thing that makes sense to me is that they rechecked your
grades.
迈克: 为什么这里的所有人都要把它朝着最坏的方面想?
Mike: Why does everybody assume the worst here?
杰森:因为我们正在谈论的就是你,迈克.
Jason: Because it's you we're talking about, Mike.
迈克: 实际上,我明天要去那儿教书.
Mike: As a matter of fact, I am going there tomorrow to teach.
杰森:哈哈.
Jason: Ha ha.
迈克:不不,爸爸,
Mike: No, no, look Dad, with this flu thing going around,
因为最近流感流行,学校这个学期需要一些替补老师.
the school system needs some substitute teachers.
开萝尔:但是他们没有叫我啊!
Carol: And they didn't call me!
迈克:开萝尔,他们可能那样做了,
Mike: Well, they probably did Carol,
但是你那时心不在焉.
but your head was in the toilet at the time.
杰森:迈克,你真的想回杜威高中,
Jason: Mike, you really wanna go back to Dewey and face the man who set
真的想去面对那个在你毕业那天燃放烟花的那个男人?
off fireworks the day you graduated?
迈克:爸爸,当我签字的时候,我并不知道我将要去杜威.但是,那个男人,杜威特先生 ,当他看到我时我想他肯定会发疯的.我打赌我肯定猜得出他见到我想说的第一句话.
Mike: I didn't know it was going to be Dewey when I signed up, Dad.But, oh man, Mr.Dewitt is gonna go nuts when he sees me.I bet you I know exactly what he's gonna say...
克丽丝:  ****!
Chrissy: ****!
迈克:不对,那只是他心里在想的.
Mike: No, but that's what he'll be thinking.
杜威特: 好了,各位!这里有人教过英语吗?
Dewitt: Alright people!Does anyone here have any experience with English?
西班牙人:是.校长.
Spaniard: habla Inglese
杜威特:我为什么没有得流感呢?
Dewitt: Why couldn't I get the flu,
不仅仅只是这24小时中的一小时患流感!
and not just one of those twenty four hour deals!
秘书:哦,
Secretary: Oh, we still need somebody to cover Mr.
我们现在仍然需要有人能代替海斯曼先生的特别课程.
Hessman's very special ed classes.
杜威特:行了,你们当中谁懂军事艺术?
Dewitt: Right, the thugs.Do any of you know martial arts?
老师:我知道 马歇尔 舒格瓦兹.
Supply Teacher: I know Marshall Schwartz.
杜威特:不要说了.
Dewitt: Close enough.
迈克:哦,打扰一下, 杜威特先生, 劳威特教练说要向您汇报一下课后留校的事情.
Mike: Ah, excuse me.Mr.Dewitt, Coach Lovett said to report to you for detention.
杜威特:西维尔,不是现在,我现在正在忙替补老师的事情…啊!!
Dewitt: Not now, Seaver, I'm busy with the substitutes...Arrgghh!!
迈克:我回来了.
Mike: I'm back.
杜威特:西维尔,你在这里干什么?
Dewitt: Seaver, what are you doing here?
迈克: 我啊,我回来教书.现在我们是同事了.
Mike: Well, I came back to teach.We're colleagues now.
杜威特:等等!等等!艾丝特,帮我做些事.
Dewitt: Get away!Get away!Estelle, do something for a change.
秘书:哦!欢迎迈克回来!
Secretary: Oh!!Welcome back Mike!!
杜威特:当然不是!
Dewitt: Not that!What makes you think I would turn over a class to a thug
是什么让你以为我会把一个班级交给象你这样的暴徒?西维尔先生,
like you?Mr.Seaver, if someone is going to teach at this school,
任何想在这间学校任教的老师都必须有素质.
they have got to be qualified.
迈克∶那这是一个新政策了.
Mike: Oh, so this is a new policy then.
杜威特∶出去!
Dewitt: Get out.
迈克∶没问题,我出席了,所以我就应该拿到我的钱.
Mike: OK, fine.At least I showed up, so I get my money.
杜威特∶太好了,我自己掏腰包.
Dewitt: Great, from my own pocket.
迈克∶太好了,比教书容易多了.
Mike: Great, this is even easier than teaching.
杜威特∶你说什么?
Dewitt: Pardon me?
秘书∶他说...
Secretary: He said...
杜威特∶我知道他说什么!你认为教书很容易!
Dewitt: I know what he said!You think teaching is easy!
迈克:是的.就是站在一群孩子前面,要知道……
Mike: Well, yeah.You just get up in front of a bunch of kids and you, you know...
杜威特∶教书!
Dewitt: Teach.
迈克∶对.
Mike: Right.
杜威特∶所以是...容易的.
Dewitt: And that's...easy.
迈克∶但是,还是没有这样来的容易.杜威特先生,我的50块.
Mike: Well, no quite as easy as this.My fifty Dollars please.Mr.Dewitt.
杜威特∶细想一下,西维尔,我今天可以用你这样的人来教书.
Dewitt: Come to think of it, Seaver, I could use somebody like you today.
迈克∶这么说,你想我留下来了?
Mike: Oh, so you want me to stick around?
杜威特∶哦,是的.
Dewitt: Oh, yes.Estelle, why don't we give our old friend Mr.Seaver...
艾丝特,为什么我们不把海斯曼先生的特别的学生交给西维尔先生呢?
oh...Mr.Hessman's very special students?
秘书∶你要让他一个人,赤手空拳的进去.
Secretary: You want to send him in, alone and un-armed.
杜威特∶噢呼.
Dewitt: Uh hu.
代课教师∶我要教什么?
Supply Teacher: Well what am I gonna teach?
杜威特∶俄语!
Dewitt: Russian.
代课教师∶可我不会说俄语.
Supply Teacher: Well I don't speak Russian.
杜威特∶没人会说,所以这是为什么这个课一直都没有人代的原因.振作起来!呃..
Dewitt: neither does anyone in the class, that's why they're taking it.
其余的人,互相学习,我不管.
Snap out of it!Err...the rest of you, heck, teach each other, I don't care.
迈克∶海斯曼一定是新来的,他是教什么的?
Mike: So, err...this Hessman guy must be new, what does he teach?
杜威特∶罪犯,主要地.
Dewitt: Criminals, mostly.
迈克∶海斯曼先生是...
Mike: Is this Mr.Hessman's...
斯库∶迈克!
Scuzz: Mike!
迈克∶斯库!嘿,你好吗,老朋友?
Mike: Scuzz!Hey, how you doing, you old scuzzmeister?
斯库∶六年的麦维尔·杜威,仍然还在继续!
Scuzz: Well, six years of Dewey and still going strong!
迈克∶耶.
Mike: Yeah.
斯库∶我今年可能可以毕业的.
Scuzz: This year, I might make it.
迈克∶哦,毕业?
Mike: Oh, yeah, graduation?
斯库∶不是,邵斯莫尔.嘿,这是迈克西维尔!我们曾经在一起上过新生英语课.
Scuzz: No, Southmoor.Hey, guys, this is Mike Seaver!We was in Freshman's English together
迈克∶当然!2次.
Mike: We sure was!Twice.
学生∶哇哇!是迈克西维尔,88班的?
Student: Wow wow!This is Mike Seaver, class of Eighty eight?
迈克∶是的,是我.
Mike: Yeah, that's me.
学生∶哇!!
Students: Wow!!
学生2∶我们都听说过你的事迹呢.嘿,当你和泊尔瞬间就把学校所有的厕所都堵住的时候,我的哥哥正在上一号呢.
Student 2: Wow, I've heard stories about you, man.Hey, my big brother was in stall number one, the day you and Boner got all the toilets in the whole school to back up at once.
迈克∶也许不是瞬间.
Mike: Well, maybe not all at once.
学生∶嘿,你是我的榜样了!
Student: Hey, you've been my role model, man!
迈克∶嘿,谢谢.
Mike: Hey, thanks.
学生2∶据说他们让你毕业,是为了要摆脱你?
Student 2: And is it true they graduated you, just to get rid of you?
迈克∶听谁说的?
Mike: Where'd you hear that?
斯库∶你在这里是一个传奇人物.
Scuzz: You're a legend here, man.
杰森∶是吗?
Mike: Yeah?
学生2∶现在他是我们的老师,太好了!
Student 2: And now he's our teacher.Alright!
学生∶嘿,我从来都没想过会有这么一个酷老师.
Student: Hey, I don't think I ever had a cool teacher before.
迈克∶谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
学生∶跟我们说说你那段偷溜进女生更衣室,并把摄像机放进里面的时光.
Student: Oh, oh, you got to tell us about the time you snook the camera into the girls locker rooms.
迈克∶什么时光?
Mike: Which time?
学生2∶告诉我们你杀死先生布格西斯先生的时光!
Student 2: Tell us about the time you killed Mr.Buginshoes!
迈克∶恩,有一点不成体统了!
Mike: Well, that was blown a little out of proportion!
学生2∶耶!
Student 2: Yeah!
学生∶出去,迈克!
Student: Get out o' here, Mike!
迈克∶嘿,我们可以有很多时间来说这些好玩的事情,不是吗?但是,首先我们得先把这份小测试做完.
Mike: Hey, look guys, there's plenty of time for fun stories, right?But first we got to get this quiz out of the way.
学生∶哈!?什么?决不.
Students: Huh?What?No way.
迈克∶嘿,嘿,
Mike: Hey, hey, look guys, come on, this was not my idea.
好了.这可不是我的主意.
Now just pass these things out.
现在把试卷传出去.如果有谁需要我帮忙削铅笔的话,就....!
If you need help sharpening your pencils, then....Good one guys!
嘿,试卷到那里去了?
Hey, where's the quizzes?
学生∶烟!火!烟!
Students: Smokey!Fire!Smokey!
迈克∶我知道就在这里.杜威特先生,你好.
Mike: I know it's here somewhere.Ah, hi, Mr.Dewitt.Hey.
杜威特∶已经遇见难题了,西维尔?
Dewitt: Problems already, Seaver?
迈克∶不,不,不,一点也没有,先生.
Mike: Ah, no, no, not at all, sir.
杜威特∶你让他们开始考试了?
Dewitt: You got them to take the quiz?
迈克∶我一把火烧了那些试卷.
Mike: Well, let's just say, I lit a fire under 'em.
杜威特∶好的!
Dewitt: Good.
迈克∶这个并不好玩,这里有火,可能有人已经被烧伤了.
Mike: Come on Guys!Guys!That was not funny, there was a fire, somebody could
have gotten hurt
迈克∶不放过我吧,行吗?不就是一个简单的测试嘛.
Mike: Guys, give me a break, alright?It's just a simple test.
斯库∶迈克,怎么告诉你呢;我们会先完一圈扑克,
Scuzz: Mike, tell you what; we'll play one round of Poker,
然后再开始做测试.
and then we're gonna take the test.
迈克∶太好了,谢谢,我万分感激!
Mike: Great, hey, thanks, I appreciate this.
斯库∶你说的.
Scuzz: Your deal.
斯库∶不错的游戏,迈克.
Scuzz: Great game, Mikey.
迈克∶好的,谢谢.我感觉我自己是在为某些事情而受罚.
Mike: Great, thanks.Man, I feel like I'm being punished for something.
杜威特∶不错,不错.
Dewitt: You are.You are.
因为你让我度过了那些地狱般的日子,你让我以前所有的同事都离开了这份高贵的职业,
You're being punished for all those years of hell you put me through.
所以,你要因此受到处罚.
You're being punished for all my former colleagues who've been driven
你还记得威斯尔先生吗,他是我请到的最好的数学老师,
out of this noble profession.Do you remember Mr.
但是,他现在却去看管游戏机了.
Wessler, the best damn Math teacher I ever had, he's a game-show host now.
迈克∶杜威特先生!
Mike: Mr.Dewitt!
杜威特∶哦,等等,迈克,我让你觉得不好过?
Dewitt: Oh, wait a second, Mike, I'm making you feel bad.
迈克∶是的...
Mike: Well, yeah.
杜威特:没有一个人肯听你的.
Dewitt: Oh and after none of those kids in there would listen to you.
迈克∶噢,我是说...
Mike: Uh hu.I mean...
杜威特∶你是很真诚的要跟他们一起.
Dewitt: You were being honest with them.
迈克∶我是的.
Mike: I was.
杜威特∶他们才不会让你好好的站在讲台上,轻轻松松的让你拿钱呢!
Dewitt: And they didn't have the decency to stand up there and get your easy money,
教书!
teaching!
迈克∶是的.
Mike: Yeah.
杜威特∶哈哈哈哈,你这个讨厌的家伙.
Dewitt: Ha ha ha ha, you little twerp.
自从我的蜜月以来,我还从来没有这么满足过!!!
I haven't been this satisfied since my honeymoon!!!
迈克∶给我点时间,杜威特先生,这才是我的第一堂课.
Mike: Well, come on, give me a break, Mr.Dewitt, this is my first class.
杜威特∶哦!你认为事情会变得简单些吗?这本来是一个要求早上8点上课的班,可是那些棘手的家伙们是不到12点不会起床的.
Dewitt: Oh, what do you think it's gonna get easier?That was an eight a.m class.The tough guys don't even get up till noon.
迈克∶我会先把我自己叫醒,我只是很少破坏我恢复过来的精力.你知道我的意思.
Mike: Yeah, well I'm just waking up myself, alright, and I'm just barely breaking my second wind.You know what I mean.
杜威特∶你甚至不可能会教的过今天!你会被撕裂的,西维尔,你会被撕裂的!而我会等在这里来践踏你的碎片.
Dewitt: You're not even gonna make it through the day!You'll crack, Seaver, you'll crack!And I'm gonna be here to stomp on the pieces.
迈克∶哦!耶!
Mike: Oh yeah!
杜威特∶第二回合!把他们拿下!
Dewitt: Round two.Go get 'em!
迈克∶嘿!嘿!不!都安静下来!谢谢,在我们开始玩之前,让我们先做完这些测试.
Mike: Hey!Hey!No!You guys be quiet!Thanks.Look, before we have any fun, we gotta get these quizzes out of the way.
学生∶嘿,迈克西维尔,真的是你吗?
Pupil: Hey, Mike Seaver, it really is you!
迈克∶是的!
Mike: Yeah!
学生∶嘿,嘿.我们为你准备了点小东西.当然不是苹果,但是,我们认为你会用的着.
Pupil: Hey, hey look man.We wanted to get you a little something.It's not an apple, but we figured it's something you could use.
学生∶喔!!!
Pupils: Woooo!!!
迈克∶嘿!
Mike: Hey!Hey!
麦琪∶克莉丝,这是词典,里面有各种各样的词...很美的词,干净的词.
Maggie: OK, Chrissy, this is a dictionary, and it's filled with words...wonderful words, clean words.
开萝尔∶妈妈,拖把在哪里?
Carol: Mom, where's the mop?
麦琪∶哦,我不知道.
Maggie: Oh, I'm airing out from the last time.
开萝尔∶又是下一次.好了,我去找.
Carol: Well it's the next time again.I'll get it.
麦琪∶这本书的优点在于,克莉丝,
Maggie: Well the beauty of this book, Chrissy,
你可以说里面的任何一个词而不会让妈咪生气.
is that you can say any word in it, and you won't make Mommy mad.
开萝尔∶妈妈,你在干什么?
Carol: Mom, what are you doing?
麦琪∶哦,我在教克莉丝关于英语语言的美丽.克莉丝,
Maggie: Oh, I'm teaching Chrissy the beauty of the English language.
随便翻一页.克莉丝,哦,
OK, Chrissy, pick any page here you want.Chrissy.Look, what page?
这一页,好.现在你可以随便指一个.
OK, that's good.Now, point to any word here at all.
克莉丝∶咕咕.
Chrissy: Goo goo.
麦琪∶好,好,很好.现在,那个单词是....怎么样查字典呀?我直到21岁才知道那个词.直到上星期六,我才又知道了另外一个.克莉丝.让我们再看看另外一个词,好吗?
Maggie: Good, good, that's very good.Now, that word is...How did that word get
in the dictionary?I didn't know that word until I was twenty one.I didn't
know I had one until last Saturday.Chrissy, let's pick another word.OK
克莉丝:****!
Chrissy: ****!
开萝尔:妈妈!
Carol: Mom!
麦琪∶我们必须显示我们一点也不烦闷,否则她会一直说这个词.
Maggie: It's important to show that we're not upset, or she'll be using this word all the time.
克莉丝:****!
Chrissy: ****!
迈克∶这是海斯曼先生的卫生课.其他的人都去哪里了?
Mike: So, this is Mr.Hessman's Health class.Where's everybody else?
学生∶他们都生病了.
Student: The big kids are sick.
迈克∶不应该这么棘手吧.既然我们已经在这里了,我们为什么不继续我们的测试呢?嘿,嘿,你去哪里?
Mike: Ah.This shouldn't be so tough.Well, as long as we're here, why don't
we go ahead and take this test, right?Hey, hey, where are you going
学生∶我?
Student: Me?
迈克∶是的.
Mike: Yeah.
学生∶把这个移开.
Student: To have this removed.
迈克∶一个孩子.我甚至连一个都搞不定.
Mike: One kid.I can't even get one kid to listen to me.
杜威特∶你也不行.
Dewitt: (on the PA) You either.
迈克∶是谁?
Mike: Who's that?
杜威特∶我是布格斯先生的灵魂.
Dewitt: I am the ghost of Mr.Buginshoes.
迈克∶你知道我根本没有杀你.你只是搬到新泽西州去卖保险了!
Mike: Hey look, look, you know I didn't kill you.You just moved to New Jersey to sell insurance!
杜威特∶是的!
Dewitt: Yeah!
迈克∶杜威特先生,是你吗?
Mike: Mr.Dewitt, is that you?
杜威特∶哈,听出我的声音了,西维尔.
Dewitt: Ha, you got me, Seaver.
迈克∶你在广播里收听我的课吗?
Mike: Hey, have you been listening in on my classes?
杜威特:你来我的办公室,我给你五十元,你可以回家了.
Dewitt: And taping 'em for the drive home.I'll tell you what Mr.Seaver, you give up now, come to my office, I'll give you the fifty Bucks now, and you can go home.
迈克∶不.
Mike: No.
杜威特∶好吧,100美元.西维尔先生,不要和我耍把戏.
Dewitt: OK, a hundred.Mr.Seaver, don't play coy with me.
我知道你正在考虑,还有,不要跟我做那个猥亵的手势.
I know you're considering it, and don't make that obscene gesture to me.
迈克:好的,我们要考试.
Mike: Alright, guys, we're gonna take this test and then...Oh, oh err...hi ladies.
少女∶喔!!!!
Girls: Woo!!!!
迈克∶小姐们,小姐们,请.
Mike: Ladies, ladies, please.
少女∶喔!!
girls: Woo!!
迈克∶(在他的脑海里)最后一堂课了,迈克,你可以搞定.你还从来没让杜威特打败过,今天也不例外.
Mike: (In his head) Last class, Mike, you can get through this.Come on, you've never let Dewitt beat you, you can't start today.
杜威特∶(在迈克的脑海里)是的,你可以西维尔先生.
Dewitt: (In Mike's head) Yes you can Mr.Seaver.
迈克∶(在他的头脑里)杜威特先生,你在我的脑海里做什么?
Mike: (In his head) Mr.Dewitt, what are you doing in my head?
杜威特∶(在迈克的脑海里)西维尔先生,我无处不在.
Dewitt: (In Mike's head) Mr.Seaver, I'm everywhere.
学生∶喔!西维尔!
Students: Wooo!Seaver!
迈克∶斯库,嘿斯库,等一下,你不是这个班的.
Mike: Scuzz, hey Scuzz, wait a minute, you're not in this class.
斯库∶当我听说是你来教时,我就决定来听听.
Scuzz: When I heard you was teaching it, I decided to audit it.
杰森∶恩,我也是.
Student: Yeah, me too.
斯库:消息传开了……
Scuzz: And then the word started spreading, this was the place to be and then...
学生∶喔!
students: Wooo!!
学生2∶迈克,我从AV室找到了这张碟,
Student 2: Mikey, I liberated this from the AV room,
我想我们可以检查一下这个记录片.
I figured we could check out this documentary.
迈克∶西班牙女牛仔.
Mike: Cowgirls in Spain.
学生2∶是哦,是哦.啤酒正在买来的路上.
Student 2: Yippee yaw yey!Oh, and the beer's on its way.
学生∶这将是今年最好的聚会.
Pupil: This'll be the best party of the year.
学生∶好!
Students: Alright!
学生∶嘿,你是一个受欢迎的老师,迈克!
Pupil: Hey, you're a very popular teacher, Mike!
学生∶耶!
Students: Yeah!!!
迈克∶我不是老师,好吧?
Mike: I am not a teacher, alright?
斯库:你是.
Scuzz: You bet you aint.
这很好.
And that's the beauty of this deal;
因为我们有一个和我们一样的老师.
for once we've got someone behind the big desk, who's like us.
学生∶耶!
Students: Yeah!!
迈克∶我不像你们.
Mike: I'm not like you.
学生2∶嘿,拉上窗帘,是学习的时间了,上课.
Student 2: Hey, pull the shades, it's time to learn something, class.
迈克∶关掉电影,好吗?
Mike: Turn off the movie, alright?
学生∶哇!!
Students: Wow!!
斯库∶对的,等迈克先找个好地方坐下来.
Scuzz: That's right, you wait until Mike gets a good seat.
迈克∶我不像你们.
Mike: Hey, I am not like you.
斯库∶哦,没关系.我们也在看这部电影.
Scuzz: Oh, that's OK, we got one of those films too.
学生∶表演时间!
Student 2: Show time!
迈克∶不属于这个班的人,都给我出去!
Mike: Whoever does not belong in this class, get out!
斯库∶迈克,你开始有点像个老师了.
Scuzz: Woo!Mikey, you're starting to sound like a teacher.
迈克∶我是一个老师!至少现在是.
Mike: Look, I am a teacher!At least for right now, OK?
所以,如果你不是这个班的,都给我出去!
So if you don't belong in here, get out!
斯库∶你怎么了?
Scuzz: What's happened to you, man?
迈克∶我成熟了.不要再笑了.在最后一排的你,你不敢把铅笔放在你的鼻子后面吧...伙计们,我今天看够了小丑了.
Mike: I grew up.Hey, cut out the laughing, alright?You in the back of row, don't you dare put those pencils up the back of your nose, buddy, I've had enough clowning around today.
学生∶你怎么会知道我是要把它们放在我的鼻子上的?
Pupil: How'd you know I Was gonna put 'em up my nose?
迈克∶因为饿哦以前也做过,事实上我还做过,
Mike: Because I've seen it before, in fact I've done it,
并且我做的很好,4支铅笔和一个自动记分器.
and I've done it better; four pencils and magic marker.
学生∶对不起.
Pupil: Sorry.
迈克∶好,我们现在先来看看能不能做点测试.如果你们女孩子认为你可以把答案写在某些我不会看的地方,那你就错了.放下被吐上唾沫的球,先生!
Mike: Alright, now let's see if we can get some work done.And if you girls think you have answers written in places I won't look, I've looked.And drop the spit ball Mr.!
学生∶但是我....
Student: But I was...
迈克∶不要告诉我你正在伸懒腰,好吧?
Mike: Don't tell me you were just stretching, alright?
学生∶是,先生!
Student: Yes, sir!
迈克∶我们现在要进行考试,接下来如果还有谁说与考试无关的事情,今天就会被留下来,并且所有的人都得留下来.清楚了吗?好,把这些往后传,不是所有的,留一张下来!
Mike: We have got a test to take today, and the next person who says
something not related to this test gets detention,
and that goes for all of you
Is that clear?Good.Pass these back.Not all of them, keep one
学生∶哦,是先生.
Student: Oh, yes sir.
迈克∶好了,不许说话!我马上回来!你,铅笔鼻,由你来负责!
Mike: Alright people, not a word till I get back.And you, pencil nose, you're in charge!
学生∶我!我不能当老师,我讨厌老师.
Pupil: Me!I can't be the teacher, I hate teachers.
迈克∶振作一点.我们必须快点,
Mike: Snap out of it.
因为我已经控制住了这些孩子,
Can we make this quick,
但是,我不知道能维持多久.
I've got these kids under control and I don't know how long it's gonna last.
杜威特∶好,可以等.
Dewitt: Oh, OK, this can wait.Seaver, what are you trying to pull?
西维尔,你拉什么?不要表现的好像你很在乎教室里会发生什么事情一样.
Don't act like you care what goes on in this room.
迈克:杜威特,他们在做小测验,
Mike: Well, Mr.Dewitt, they're taking a quiz, I mean,
这不是你想要的么?
isn't that' what you wanted?
杜威特:你想让你想象你上学时候讨厌的老师.我想让你在冰冷的红色地板的屋里痛哭,就像我每天早上在办公室那样.
Dewitt: I wanted you to feel bad about every teacher you mistreated in
your academic career!And I use that term in its broadest sense.
I wanted you to crack and cry like a baby on a cold vermilion floor,
like I do in my office every morning.
迈克∶不是有地毯吗?
Mike: Isn't it carpeted?
杜威特∶是有.西维尔!
Dewitt: Well yes it is...Seaver!
迈克∶眼睛看你的试卷!你是说...
Mike: Eyes on your papers, people!You were saying...
杜威特∶我在说,等等,你希望我爱上你的表演吗?你肯定是付钱给了所有的人.
Dewitt: I was saying...Wait a minute, you expect me to fall for this act?You're paying these people off, of course.
迈克∶杜威特先生,我没有给任何人钱.就算我给了,也不会奏效.你知道,我试着和他们一起玩,我试着对他们好点,我试着心平气和,但是,唯一能制服他们的却是我的粗野和铁一样的拳头!
Mike: Mr.Dewitt, I...I'm not paying anyone off, alright?And even if I did, it wouldn't have worked.You know, I've tried being funny with these people, I've tried being nice, I've tried being cool, but the only thing that ever got through to them was when I was an...an uncool, iron-fisted tyrant!
杜威特∶暴君?
Dewitt: Tyrant?
迈克∶是的.
Mike: Yeah.
杜威特∶西维尔,你刚才用了1个双音节词.
Dewitt: Seaver, you just used a two syllable word.
迈克∶这就是为什么老师不能太冷静的原因!也是为什么你是个白痴的原因!
Mike: That's why teachers can't be cool!That's why you're such a bozo!
杜威特∶对的....
Dewitt: That's righ...
迈克:杜威特,我有事情要跟你说.
Mike: Mr.Dewitt, look, I've got something to tell you;
教学非常难.
teaching is a tough job!!
杜威特∶不!
Dewitt: No!
迈克∶我还要告诉你的事,明天要参加考试的那些孩子们,
Mike: You know, I got another thing to say;
先生...
it's that those kids are gonna take that test tomorrow, if it kills me.
你最好给我一个很好的理由,来解释你为什么离开你的座位,
Mr.you better have a real good reason for being out of your seat, and Mr.
还有你,
get your ears away from this door,
不要再在门边偷听了,因为这次谈话和你一点关系也没有.
as this conversation has nothing to do with you!
杜威特∶太好了,懦夫小姐.
Dewitt: Good golly, Miss Molly.
迈克∶什么?
Mike: What?
杜威特∶当我们老师们在一起的时候,
Dewitt: There's a theory among educators that we all talk about when we
会经常讨论一个教育工作者的理论,
gather at the...teacher place.
如果我们能把一个捣蛋鬼,
The theory goes like this; if we could take one of our goof-offs,
就是那些耗尽我们精力的人治服的话,那么被改造好的学生就会用他的能力来做好事情,
the ones who suck up our energy and give nothing back.
而不会去做坏事情.
If we could take such a student and turn him so that he could use his
他以后也会成为一个好老师.
powers for good instead of evil, he, oh he, would be the perfect teacher...
你就是我们一直在等的那个完美的老师.
the one!The one, we've always been waiting for.You could be this man.
迈克∶我,完美的老师?
Mike: Me, a perfect teacher?
杜威特∶酷,不是吗?
Dewitt: Chilling, isn't it?
迈克∶杜威特先生,我不知道该怎么样来完美,
Mike: Well, Mr.Dewitt, I don't know about being perfect,
但是,我肯定我自己闻起来像个老师.
but I sure smell like a teacher.
杜威特∶汗臭味与便宜衣服的混合,我很清楚的.
Dewitt: Ah, yes, the mixture of flop sweat and cheap clothing, I know it well.
迈克∶嘿,杜威特先生,对曾经给你带来的悲痛,我真的深感抱歉..
Mike: Hey, look Mr.Dewitt, I'm really sorry for all the grief I ever gave you...
杜威特∶迈克,如果你是我们要等的完美老师,其他事都不重要了.
Dewitt: Well Mike, if you're the one, none of that matters.
迈克∶我是说,
Mike: Well, you know, I mean,
我在你背后说的那些坏话,
all of the stuff I said behind your back and like the time that I put
还有把PA放在你的私人浴室....
the...the PA mike in your private bathroom...
杜威特∶哦,迈克,对...那是你!!
Dewitt: Oh Mike yes....That was you!!
迈克∶是的.
Mike: Yeah.
杜威特∶西维尔先生...
Dewitt: Mr.Seaver...
迈克∶我要去看看我的班了,
Mike: I got to go check on my class, alright?
谢谢你对我的赞美.
And thank you for all the nice things you said about me.
杜威特∶也许一切都是我们的想象,也许我精神恍惚.我知道,
Dewitt: Maybe I am imagining all this.Maybe I am hallucinating.
我肯定是感冒了.一定是.我要离开这里.
I know, I have the flu.I do.I have the flu.I'm out of here.
杰森:等一下,放松点.
Jason: Wait a minute, slow down.You've had quite a day now, just take it easy.
你今天很辛苦,
You've learned something today, nobody ever thought you would...
放松.你学到了很多.
especially your parents.The question is,
听我说,你不要再说这话了,
what are you gonna do with all this new found knowledge?
好么?
Listen to me, now are you not to use that word in this house again,
克莉丝∶… 00:22:07,200
now do we have a deal? Chrissy: ...